[Music]
hi
i'm rudy manik chief female resources
and marketing officer of fw insurance
indonesia being awarded as one of the
best companies to work for in asia 2022
is an honor for us as it shows our
continued support in supporting our
employees to pursue their unstoppable
patients in fw insurance we strive to
become an inclusive work environment
through our values of being committed
innovative proactive open and caring
i want to thank our employees the
trailblazers and leadership team
for their continuous dedications and
consistent contributions to the company
we believe this award will motivate us
to achieve our visions in changing the
way people feel about insurance
and invite more people
to celebrate living thank you
[Music]